Nighttime and Idol
Looks like a lot of work
Well, it's time for the ending!
Here comes the ending!
Thank you very much.
I know I said I didn't want to talk, but thank you for talking at all.
Did I hit the nail on the head? Yes.
No, no, no, no, we were engaged. I thought we were engaged, too.
I was just wondering how often you have conversations where you talk so much but have no substance.
I think he's making fun of me.
Is it bearing fruit?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on, Mr. Dandy.
Yes, sir.
Would you like to give us the news, please?
Okay, I'll read the appraisal.
The whole country... don't laugh.
That's a new one.
This is a new one.
Starting on Sunday, March 4th at the Miyagi Sendai Pit, we'll be in Kanagawa, Hyogo, Osaka, Aichi, Chiba, Saitama, Fukuoka, Hiroshima...
Kanagawa, Hyogo, Osaka, Aichi, Chiba, Saitama, Fukuoka, Hiroshima.
These are the places I want to go.
Then around Hokkaido, Friday, May 19 and Saturday, May 20.
Live?
Oh, Line?
Line Cube
The final show will be held at Line Cube Shibuya!
Please come and join us!
How many places are there?
One, two, three...
Eleven locations.
At the end, we'll have a cup of tea from the kettle.
You can drink the tea that comes out of the kettle.
Is the tea okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Do you mean that you're going to drink the tea that comes out of this talking thing?
Yes, the tea comes from here.
Today's tea is Oji tea, which makes you feel relieved, windy, and refreshed.
It also has jasmine tea in it.
It smells so good.
Yes, yes.
It's hot.
Bon appétit.
Yes, please.
Is tea okay?
Here you go.
Oh, it's good!
Oh, good!
Delicious! I'll have this!
Oh! By all means, take it home.
I'm sure you'll like it.
It's delicious.
It's okay if you get wind of it nicely.
Yes, sir. And I thought it would be good after the meat.
No, it's good.
The tea is a palate cleanser.
Thank you very much.
Come on, just like that.
Oh, thank you very much. Thank you for staying with us for so long.
No, thank you very much.
I knew I was dealing with such a noisy guy.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Very much so. I knew it, Mr. Gull. If you could just finish up by looking cute for the camera...
If you could just close with a cute ending for the camera, that would be the end of that closing, right, Mr. Gal?
Yes, please do.
I would really appreciate it.
Yes.
Well, everyone, this is the Year of the Rabbit.
Thank you very much.
Binara, thank you.
I've been instructed to do it, right here, right now.
I see.
Okay.
To the end.
Like this.
That's what idols do.
There are no pretty faces.
I'm learning.
Thank you very much.
This program is...
Momochan.
Suzu-san who would like to be given a flower circle
Mr. Pei
Yo-chan-san
Harupyon provided this program!
Thank you all!
Thank you